mobileheadlines.net 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Mobileheadlines

Privacy Policy for mobileheadlines.net

If you need any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us via e-mail

admin@mobileheadlines.net

This privacy policy confines the types of personal information is received and collected by [Mobileheadlines.net](https://www.mobileheadlines.net/) and how it is used.

The privacy of our visitors to Mobileheadlines.net is important to us. So, we have developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect data and how we will use that data for the future purpose. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before collecting personal information, we will seriously identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use personal information only for the purpose of achieving those purposes that are determined by us and are compatible for other purposes unless we have the consent of the person concerned or required by law.
  * We will collect personal information in fair and legal ways, with the consent of the individual concerned.
  * We will keep personal information only as long as necessary to achieve those purposes.
  * Personal data must be related to the purposes that can be used
  * We are committed to protecting personal information through security assurances against loss or theft.
  * We will also provide customers with information on our personal information management policies

By registering on the mailing list, the privacy of your mailing address will remain respected and will not be published.

**Cookies and network counters**

Our site uses cookies to store information about visitor settings, and specific user information is recorded when entering or visiting a page, and the content of a Web page is customized based on the browser type of visitors or other information when the visitor sends information to the browser.

**Links to other websites**

Our site may include links to other websites. or from other sites such as Google AdSense and we do not consider that they are responsible for data collection methods by those sites. You can see the privacy policies and content of those sites that are accessed through any link within this site.

We may hire third-party advertising companies to display ads when you visit our website. These companies have the right to use information about your visits to this site and to other websites, except the name, phone number or address, email address, in order to make announcements about the goods and services that interest you. If you want more information about this as well as if you want to know what choices are available to you to prevent this information from being used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Contact Us**

You can contact us by clicking on the Contact Us link available on our site links
